Thank goodness, Nezuko's asleep.
Nezuko! No, don't!
You sleep tight, Nezuko.
I can still move, I can still put up a fight, and this time, no matter what happens, I'm fighting
to the very end!
Nezuko! No, don't!
But that's the end of the day, I'm just there.
I'm going to be the same, I'm going to be the same, and this time, no matter what happens, I'm going to be the same.
Here you go!
光も闇も怒りも全部抱きしめて
選ばれなければ選べばいい
声を枯らして燃える花の花に
波を照らしたら
曖昧すぎる世界を想いにして
夜を数えて朝を描くような
鮮やかな目を鳴らす
どんなに深い後悔も
どんなに高い限界も
かき消して
残響
ご視聴ありがとうございました
You have no idea. This country of ours. It's giant. It's full of people who would blow your mind.
Some are a complete mystery. They can pick up a sword and become a Hashiro in just two months.
Yet you're saying I'm special? What a load of crap!
Do you have any idea just how many lives have slipped through my fingers?
That's right. Rengoku is always ahead of me in that regard.
Meh. If you aren't special, then what's going on? Both of my bloodsicles are drenched with deadly poison.
I'm positive it's entered your bloodstream by now, so why aren't you dead?
I said I'm a trained shinobi, didn't I? I'm immune to nearly all types of poison.
The shinobi were wiped out back during the Edo period, you fool. Don't think you can lie to us.
It's not a lie.
The shinobi still exists. I had nine brothers and sisters.
Seven died by the time I turned 15.
Frightened that our clan would live on only in history, my father forced us to train as if our lives depended on it.
The only survivors were myself and my brother two years younger than me.
And he was exactly like my father.
They shared the same mindset, treating subordinates like pawns.
His wives were no exception. He just wanted heirs. No one else ever had any say. His word was absolute.
And I... I didn't want to become like him.
It's hard, isn't it, Tengen? The path that you've chosen.
You've decided to reject the very same values that shaped you into the shinobi you are today.
And enter the battlefield where those values thrive.
It must be painful.
Despite carrying all that conflict within yourself, still, you all insist on pushing forward and fighting.
And for a noble cause, too.
All so you can protect other people's lives.
You have my thanks.
You are quite a remarkable child.
It is I who should be giving thanks.
Master, I'd never think twice about laying down my life for your sake.
Those with conflict might be spineless fools, but it's why I've achieved everything that I have up until now.
And I've never been without it.
What the hell are you laughing about?
Slowly but surely.
The poison's affecting you after all, isn't it?
This must be embarrassing after all that talk about it not working on a guy like you, huh?
You're wrong.
I'm fine.
Look for yourself.
I've never felt better.
I could devour a hundred bowls of Tempura Dawn.
In a flashy way, of course.
Don't you dare lay a hand on my little sister!
You scumbag!
Well, those are unique explosions.
They can inflict damage on a demon's body.
And detonate from the slightest friction.
Since she slashed one without realizing that, she got hit.
There's never a dull moment taking care of her, that's for sure.
No, he's holding on to the tip of his sword.
What kind of insane grip is that?
Now!
I missed my chance to finish him!
He just beheaded me again!
Damn you!
I'll make you pay for this!
It's not fair!
Not fair!
How come I'm the one who's always getting beheaded!
Hold on.
You're on to us, aren't you, big guy?
About what?
Not that finding out about our little trick will do you any good, since you're going to
die a slow and painful death anyway.
Even now, as we speak, we're getting closer and closer to your inevitable death, aren't
we?
Are you sure about that?
Who did you forget about me?
It is I, Lordy Nostate!
Along with my trusty minion!
Who the hell are these two idiots?
Follow me if you're wounded!
That's for everyone else!
Please evacuate!
I've taught you well!
Talk about a flashy entrance!
Keep it coming!
You can summon all the underlings you want, but unfortunately your fate was sealed from the start.
So look, you are all going to die anyway, right?
So drop the act and quit staring at me like that, will ya?
There are two demons now.
How did that happen?
Also, the belt demon isn't dead.
Are they both upper six and somehow splintered off each other?
If that is the case, then there's no doubt this guy is the main threat.
His scent is different.
It's far stronger.
It feels like the back of my throat's going numb from it.
My hands won't stop shaking.
Is it because I'm exhausted?
Or is it that I'm afraid?
It doesn't matter.
Because either way,
no matter how strong they are,
we'll win!
Cause we're Demon Slayer Corps!
Yeah right, that chance!
Not when your only hope to win is being ravaged by poison!
Poison?
Does it look like I care, you idiots?
I'm at the top of my game when I got a little poison in my system!
Drop the act already!
It's no act!
You just underestimate humans!
All three of these boys are my brilliant Tsukuko!
They have relentless grit!
Yeah, we do!
And they'll fight even if their limbs fall off!
Not to mention, I've already figured out how to bring you two down!
And that's to behead the both of you!
Simultaneously!
Am I right?
That's why you don't just absorb your weaker sister completely!
Keeping your talents separate makes you harder to kill!
Ha ha!
This'll be easy peasy!
Ha ha ha!
That's as simple as that, isn't it?
Then we've already won, haven't we?
You say that, but the demon slayers who perished before you didn't find that task to be so simple!
Not even the Hashira!
Fifteen for me and seven for my sister!
That's how many we've devoured!
You heard him!
Not a single one of those fools even lived to see Daybreak!
After all, we always have the long nights on our side!
Your deaths are inevitable, so just die!
Huh?
WILL HE QUired?
Sanitsu, leave that whirlady to me and Mr. Sleepyhead!
You two focus on taking down the praying mantis looking guy!
Careful! Yeah, yeah!
I'm not about to let you kill my sister.
It's you! The little brat!
There's something I need to tell you.
Apologize to the girl whose ear you pulled.
Huh?
Even if it really was your earnings that kept the house afloat and provided for everyone,
it still doesn't make those girls your belongings.
You have no right to treat them like that.
Oh, please, don't bore me with your high and mighty lecturing.
With unfortunate looks like yours, what makes you think that you can talk down to me exactly?
In this city, women are merchandise, the same as objects.
They are bought, sold, and then discarded.
Such is the right of an owner.
Those without beauty don't deserve even a grain of rice.
It only makes sense the wretches shouldn't be treated as humans.
You shouldn't inflict the pain that was done to you onto others.
You couldn't be more wrong.
The horrible things done to us.
The things that made us suffer.
It only makes sense to give back what we received.
We might have been driven to misfortune,
but we make up for it in the revenge we exact upon the blessed.
Do you understand now?
That's the way we've chosen to live our lives.
We have killed off anyone who's ever crossed us.
Anyone who's ever slighted us.
We're going to slash through your gullets,
just like we did to all who came before you.
His bloodlust is unreal.
It's giving my whole body chills.
He's the real deal.
An upper six demon.
You have to focus.
Mr. Uzui's been poisoned, so I have to protect him.
Strike with your sword the instant he makes a move.
The second he moves even an inch.
That's my chance.
Swing it.
Swing your sword.
Evade it.
Bend backwards.
Bend.
What are you doing?
He protected you instead, and now you're just a hindrance.
I can't deflect this many belts.
She's got three eyes.
I can see everything now, including all of your movements.
Now that brother's awake, I'm able to show you what my true power looks like.
Shut up!
Your shrill voice is really making my head hurt.
Then here I thought you'd be different.
You won't get close enough to even start fighting me!
Shut up, war ladies!
If you're really as strong as you say, then why run your belt the whole time instead of killing us?
Be careful what you ask for!
I'll be careful.
I'll be careful!
I'll be careful what you ask.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ah!
Ah ah ah ah!
Ah ah!
Ah ah ah ah ah
Ach!
Ah!
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah uh.
Ah ah.
This speed! He really is like a praying mantis! And these attacks of his!
I'm trapped!
Why are these slashes so heavy?
Sidestep it! Ward off the blow!
If you take it head on, it'll snap your blade in half!
If it's power versus power, the weaker side always loses!
Don't misjudge the flow of power and redirect it as necessary!
The flexible water breathing technique is better for defense!
If I had just done this before, my blade never would have gotten chipped!
Sound breathing. Fifth form.
Straight performance!
You can use your noisy moves all you want, Hashira, but it changes nothing!
Drop dead, you ugly tomes!
Now we have blood blades flying towards us with the belt?
If this keeps up, then I'll never be able to get near the worm lady!
These damn blood blades are bad news!
I can sense that even a scratch from them would be deadly!
Try to be useful! Don't let him attack like he wants!
Most importantly, find a way to win!
He won't hold up much longer. It's a miracle he can still move at all!
That shoulder wound must be really deep. He seems to have stopped the bleeding for now.
But that left hand tied to his heels is the only thing keeping his grip.
All because I let myself get poisoned.
If I don't take care of this now, we'll be annihilated!
I can't breathe! There's too much happening to catch my breath!
I'm about to black out! I've gotta find a way to start recovery breathing!
Pff!
What's this?
Kunai?
It's gonna be a pain dealing with this many of them in front of a Hashira.
Could they be any more annoying?
There's still three fledgling demon slayers too.
Well, even if they do hit me, these things are no problem.
Wait.
Would they really try to pull off such a meaningless attack?
Blood demon art!
Rampant arc rampage!
He's creating a dome with the slashes!
Hey, hold on a second.
What's going on here?
He's closing in on me?
What's this?
There's multiple kunai stuck in him?
That's right.
He's not a swordsman, he's a shinobi.
That explains his otherworldly battle senses.
I'm going to get this.
My legs are regenerating.
I knew it, they're laced with something.
If I had to guess, this kunai is probably coated in something extracted from Wisteria.
My body's going numb.
Hey, not too shabby.
You're starting to get into sync with one another in such a short time.
How amusing!
Please.
No!
Time and 찾 voor the moon
The future is still quite weak
Tell and love and跪!
again
Kimmy or Yonde
Rengoku, how would you fight against this?
What if I'm just not able to handle this like you could?
It's okay to do things a little differently.
Rengoku, your sword skills are elegant though. You do have too many wives
The Commodore boy the yellow-haired boy and boar-headed boy take care of them who's we
Now watch over them flashily next episode nine defeating an upper-ranked demon